<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Futureworkz]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Futureworkz]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 04:22:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CUSTOMER JOURNEY MAP -WHAT CAN WE GET OUT FROM IT?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>CUSTOMER JOURNEY MAP -WHAT CAN WE GET OUT FROM IT?</h1><p>A customer journey map is a graphical representation of a customer’s total interaction and experience with an organisation or product, across both minor and major sales channels. This journey starts from when the customer becomes aware of a particular need for a service or product, through efforts on finding a solution, choosing from various options, until he/she makes a purchase. A customer journey map may not always consist of the entire start to finish sequence description we just saw; sometimes, only few elements of a customer’s experience are enough to define that particular customer’s journey map.  Whenever a customer initiates an interaction with an organisation, such interactions arise because of questions to which the customer needs answers. The effort to provide answers to such questions creates conversations between the customers and the organisation. For instance, such a conversation may consist of the organisation asking the type of questions that will help it understand customers’ needs, what they want from the organisation, and their expectations. These questions will help the customers guide the organisation on ways of fulfilling these needs.  Customers appreciate these types of conversations because they feel they have some value to create for the organisation. The customers’ needs, expectations, requirements, and suggestions become great benefits to the company, because they all combine to form the basis for the organisation to improve and create better products and services.  A customer journey map seeks to create an insight into everything a customer desires from an organisation, and helps the organisation understand the ways a customer uses its products or services. This synergy helps develop the customer’s confidence over time, with a greater possibility of well-informed feedback, which helps the organisation become a better brand, offer better and unique products and services that addresses customer needs.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>undefinedcustomer-journey-map-what-can-we-get-out-from-it/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a7545688-f61a-4c35-b5f2-6fd8715a0ffd</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 04:21:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>